Aladdin Company Records Collection 1907-1989 (bulk 1940-1982)
Clarke Historical Library
- Aladdin Company Collection - Series #5, (Construction Department)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Groveland, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 177, Folder 71)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Hartford, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 177, Folder 72)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Hillsdale, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 177, Folder 73)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Holbrook, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 178, Folder 74)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Holland, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 178, Folder 75)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Hollywood, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 178, Folder 76)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Holmes, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 178, Folder 77)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Hummel, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 179, Folder 78)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Kensington, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 179, Folder 79)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Kenton, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 179, Folder 80)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Kenwood, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 180, Folder 81)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Kimberly, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 180, Folder 82)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Kingbury, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 180, Folder 83)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Lamar, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 181, Folder 84)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Laredo, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 181, Folder 85)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Lexington, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 181, Folder 86)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Longwood, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 181, Folder 87)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Lorain, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 181, Folder 88)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Manchester, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 182, Folder 89)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Manhasset, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 182, Folder 90)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Mayflower 1927, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 182, Folder 91)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Medford, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 182, Folder 92)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Monterey, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 182, Folder 93)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Nassau, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 183, Folder 94)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Newton, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 183, Folder 95)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Normandy, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 183, Folder 96)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Oakland, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 184, Folder 97)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Orlando, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 184, Folder 98)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Palomar, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 184, Folder 99)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Parkwood, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 185, Folder 100)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Pasadena, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 185, Folder 101)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Pinecrest, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 185, Folder 102)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Plaza, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 186, Folder 103)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Portage, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 187, Folder 104)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Preston, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 187, Folder 105)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Princeton, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 187, Folder 106)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Redwood, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 188, Folder 107)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Regency, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 188, Folder 108)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Richmond, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 188, Folder 109)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Ridgewood, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 188, Folder 110)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Rio Grande, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 189, Folder 111)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Riviera, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 189, Folder 112)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Rockwood, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 189, Folder 113)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Rosewood, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 190, Folder 114)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Rotterdam, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 190, Folder 115)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Royton, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 190, Folder 116)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Salem, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 190, Folder 117)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Santa Fe, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 191, Folder 118)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Saratoga, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 191, Folder 119)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Savannah, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 191, Folder 120)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Selma, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 192, Folder 121)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Shady Lane, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 192, Folder 122)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Sharlear, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 192, Folder 123)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Shasta, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 193, Folder 124)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Shelby, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 193, Folder 125)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Sheridan, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 193, Folder 126)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Sherwood, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 193, Folder 127)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Sierra, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 194, Folder 128)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Sparta, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 194, Folder 129)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Stratford, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 195, Folder 130)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Sylvan, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 195, Folder 131)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Tacoma, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 195, Folder 132)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Topeka, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 196, Folder 133)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Trenton, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 196, Folder 134)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Tulane, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 196, Folder 135)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Ventura, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 197, Folder 136)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Ventura (cont.), 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 198, Folder 137)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Vernon, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 198, Folder 138)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Vinewood, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 199, Folder 142)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Virginia-1941, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 199, Folder 143)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Wilmington, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 200, Folder 139)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Wilshire, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 200, Folder 140)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Winslow, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 200, Folder 141)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Wonder House-1940, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 201, Folder 144)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Yorkshire, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 201, Folder 145)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Yorktown, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 201, Folder 146)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Other building types: churches, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 201, Folder 147)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Garages & Breezeways, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 202, Folder 148)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Stores, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 202, Folder 149)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Motels and Tourist Homes, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 202, Folder 150)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Details including kitchen plan schedules 1963-1978, and Aladdin plan chart – c. 1920,1920-1978 (Box 203, Folder 152)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Plan Schedules, 1963-1978 – Not in drawer,1963-1978 (Box 203, Folder 152b)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Details and kitchen, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 203, Folder 153)
  - Records, Plans for Catalog Models - Construction Charts - Details, 1927-1982 (primarily 1947-1982),1927-1982 (Box 203, Folder 151)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Alamo; No order number, Anthony Pallante, Clawson, MI 1977; Order 78-017, Mrs. Rena Thompson, Redford, MI 1978; Order 78-034, Mr. and Mrs. David Timmen, Lansing, MI 1977; Order 77-055A, Incomplete. 1977,1977-1978 (Box 204, Folder 154)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Amberwood; Order 78-038, Mr. & Mrs. Donald Mattoon, Bath, NY 1978; Order 78-002, Rev. Kenneth Smith, Deland, FL 1978,1978 (Box 204, Folder 155)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Amsterdam; No order number, Arthur Forziati, Pocasset, MA 1977; Order 77-099, Claude E. Jones, Fairplay, KY 1977; Order 79-016, Clair M. Lambert, Houlton, ME 1979,1977, 1979 (Box 204, Folder 156)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Arlington; No order number or purchases named, brick veneer front without garage,1982 (Box 204, Folder 157)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Ashland; No order number, Mr. & Mrs. Gerald Leist, Bay City, MI 1977; Order 78-018, Richard Peel, Milford, MI 1978,1977-1978 (Box 204, Folder 158)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Austin; Order 77-083, Rev. & Mrs. D.H. Bebbink, Big Rapids, MI. 1977; Order 69-046, no owner or place, 1969,1969, 1977 (Box 204, Folder 159)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Bates; No order number, Carl Baccellieri, New York, NY 1979; No order number, Rev. Douglas Clark, Gambier, OH 1977; Order 79-013, Mr. & Mrs. Allen Crawford, Florissant, MO 1979; No order number, Mr. & Mrs. Albert Henderson, Kingsville, OH 1978; Order 77-054, Glenn Herschberger, Goshen, IN 1977; Order 77-086, Mr. & Mrs. Paul Kellermeier, Perrysburg, OH 1977; Order 80-012, Arnold Kirn, no location, 1980; No order number, Joseph McKnight, no location, 1980; No order number Ralph Murray and son, Sycamore, OH 1978; Order 78-025, Mark Niendorf, Howell, MI 1978; Order 77-115, Mr. & Mrs. John Parker, Farwell, MI, 1977; Order 77-093, Michael J. Saittor, Trevose, PA 1977; Order 78-003, Mr. & Mrs. F.G. Schramer, Maple Park, IL 1978; Order 77-019, Larry Schweller, Ottawa, OH 1977; Order 78-020, Mr. & Mrs. Bob Vandercook, Ypsilanti, MI 1978; Order 77-014, no owner or place. 1977; Order 78-014, no owner or place. 1978; Order 78-043, no owner or place. 1978; Order 78-042, no owner or place. 1979,1977-1980 (Box 205, Folder 160)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Belmont; No order number, James Hoover, no place. 1981; No order number, Mr. Pat McCarthy, Highland Park, MI. 1964; Order number 78-022, Mr. & Mrs. Frank McCreary, Irwin, OH, 1978,1964-1981 (Box 205, Folder 161)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Berkeley; No order number, Kathy Donlin, Coatsville, PA, 1978; No order number, Mr. & Mrs. Michael Hasset, Chelsea, MI. 1979/1981; Order 77-035, Mr. & Mrs. Donals Herrmann, New Castle, IN 1977; Order 77-030, Atwood Ketts, Davidon, MI. 1979; Order 77-074, Mr. & Mrs. Phillip Miller, Northup, OH. 1977; No order number, John Patterson, Markham, IL, 1977; No order number, John Patterson, Markham, IL, 1977; No order number, Richard J. Reber, Plymouth, OH, 1981,1977-1981 (Box 205, Folder 162)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Briarwood; Order 77-009, Mr. & Mrs. Ken Buchanan, Lake Wortl, FL, 1976; Order 76-0061,1976, undated (Box 205, Folder 163)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Brighton; No order number, Bernard Klein, Midland, MI, 1964; No order number, John H. Stewart, Russel, PA, 1965,1964-1965 (Box 206, Folder 164)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Bronson; No order number, Morris Gwisdala, Bay City, MI, 1977,1977 (Box 206, Folder 165)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Camden; Order 79-032, Edwin H. Dean, Garden City, MI, 1979; Order 77-088, Mr. & Mrs. Lawrence Gingell, Metamora, MI, 1977; No order number, William McClanahan, Clyde, OH, (incomplete),1977-1979, undated (Box 206, Folder 166)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Canyon Garage; No order number,1968 (Box 206, Folder 167)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Catalina; Order 77-029, Mr. & Mrs. Martin Coulson, Jr., Drayton Plains, MI, 1977,1977 (Box 206, Folder 168)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Chelsea; Order 77-011, Mr & Mrs. John L. Backus, Ogdenburg, NY, 1977; No order number, Charles D. Cooper, North Madison, OH, 1982; No order number, J.J. Kesinski, Villa Park, IL, 1977; No order number, Mr. & Mrs. Howard Pyle, Potersville, PA, 1978; Order 77-078, Mr. & Mrs. Gandolfo Richiusa, Naperville, IL, 1977; Order 77-102, Virgel R. Schroeder, Ottawa, OH, 1977; No order number, Paul Walling, Anaheim, CA, 1977 (diazo prints included); Order 78-004, Incomplete, 1978 (?),1977-1982 (Box 206, Folder 169)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Coachman; Order 79-045, Mr. & Mrs. Richard Felder, Lakewood, OH, 1978; Order 80-007, Mr. & Mrs. Gerald Nilsen, Studivant, MD, 1980,1978-1980 (Box 206, Folder 170)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Cornell – MISSING as of 1-6-10; Order 77-065, Ronald Brewer, Marseilles, IL, 1977; Order 77-051, Robert Counihan, Laurel, MD, 1977; Order 79-024, Randall Jenkins, Mt. Vernon, IL, 1979; Order 77-076, Ronald Kline, Chambersburg, PA, 1977; Order 79-031, Doug McInally, Silverwood, MI, 1979; No order number, Mr & Mrs. Vincent H. Ranger, Harper Woods, MI, 1979; Order 77-111, Gary Telton, Richmond, MI, 1977,1977-1979 (Box 206, Folder 171)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Crestwood; No order number, Mr. & Mrs. Michael A Fazekas, Ringoes, NJ, 1979; Order 77-040, Mr. & Mrs. Nino Pecorado, Michigan City, IN 1977; Order 77-039, Mr. & Mrs. Dennis Reinke, Saginaw, MI, 1979; Order 79-011, Mr & Mrs. Donald Stevenson, Bay City, Bay City, MI, 1978; Order 77-044, Robert Walker, Bay City, MI, 1977; Order 77-040, 1977; Order 77-116, no owner or address, 1977,1977-1979 (Box 207, Folder 172)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Danbury; No order number, Robert Nolan, Staten Island, NY, 1978 [note: followed by Diazo print of Sierra 1 brick veneer, same owner, 1978],1978 (Box 207, Folder 173)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Delta; Order 81-006, Warren A. Taber, no address, 1981 [Diazo print included],1981 (Box 207, Folder 174)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Denton; Order 77-113, Mr. & Mrs. Spencer Redmond, Roseville, MI,1977 (Box 207, Folder 175)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Dexter; No order number, Robert L. Lowe, Marinburg, WV, 1977; Order, 77-068, John H. Miller, Emporium, PA, 1977,1977 (Box 207, Folder 176)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Dover; No order number, Theodore F. Fettig, Marian, IN, 1981; No order number, Mr. & Mrs. Michael Heilman, Carey, OH, 1979; No order number, W.F. Sovereign, Essexville, MI, 1977; Order 77-109, Alfred Trapanese, West Long Branch, NJ, 1977; No order number, Greg Vogl, no address, 1981,1977-1981 (Box 207, Folder 177)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Dunbar; Order 77-096, Betty Gerdes, Camp Hill, PA, 1976; Order 77-081, Mr. & Mrs. Keith Jordan, Decker, IN, 1977; No order number, Kenneth Lyon, Dawn, MD, 1979,1976-1979 (Box 208, Folder 178)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Eastland; No order number, Allen Bloomhutt, Blanchesterm, OH, 1978; Order 77-112, G. Richard Culp, D.O., Harrisburg, OG, 1977; Order 79-005, David Millstead, Box 67 Rt #1, Alanson, MI, 1979; Order 79-015, David M. Schwanberger, Columbus, OH, 1979,1977-1979 (Box 208, Folder 179)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Edison; No order number, Donald G. Abbey, Groton, CN,1964 (Box 208, Folder 180)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Eldorado; No order number, George M. Hama, Huntington Woods, MI, 1981; Order 80-016, Ruth Hibbard, no address, 1980; Order 80-010, Mr. Lee Valentini, no address, 1980,1980-1981 (Box 208, Folder 181)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Essex; Order 77-091, Mr. & Mrs. Tom Carlson, Silver Creek, NY,1977 (Box 208, Folder 182)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Fairlane; No order number, Alvin Kelly, Atlanta, GA, 1979; No order number, Mr. & Mrs. Brian St. Clair, New Lennox, IL, 1978; Order 78-027, Mr. & Mrs. Gary Warthen, Lemont, IL, 1978; Order 81-012, Kenneth C. Hoover, Sunbury, OH, 1981; Order 79-029, Herbert Newton, Gilbertsville, KY, 1979,1978-1981 (Box 208, Folder 183)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Gary,undated (Box 208, Folder 184)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Glenwood; Order 77-092, William Posak, Mt. Clemens, MI, 1977; Order 81-077, no name or address, 1981,1977, 1981 (Box 209, Folder 185)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Goodrich; No order number, Mr. & Mrs. Kenneth Kreider, Meyersdale, PA, 1979; Order 77-021, Mr. & Mrs. Charles Lambert, Bluefield, WV, 1977; No order number, Cleo H. Nordmeyer, Chebanse, IL, 1980; No order number, Thomas Trupino, Taylor, MI, 1978; No order number, Mr. & Mrs. Robert When, Chicago, IL, 1979,1977-1980 (Box 209, Folder 186)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Holbrook; Order 77-053, Rev. Aldolf Bickel, Napoleon, OH, 1977; Order 81-004, Arthur Burns, Chilton, WI, 1981; Order 78-007, Gerald A. Butler, Center Lane, MI 1977; Order 78-041, Kenneth Engel, Valparaiso, IN, 1978; No order number, Mr & Mrs. Clyde Leary, Plymouth, IN, 1978; Order 78-035, Mr. & Mrs. Don Malkowski, Freesoil, MI, 1978; No order number, Mr. & Mrs. Tim Matson, Chagrin Falls, OH, 1977; Order 79-009, Mr. & Mrs. E. C. Morin, Bay City, MI, 1979; Order 80-011, Steve Stedman, McGuffy, OH, 1980; No order number, Orval Wagoner, no address, 1980; Order 77-024, no owner, address, or date,1977-1980 (Box 209, Folder 187)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Holmes; Order 78-008, Mr. & Mrs. Archie Hill, Huntertown, IN, 1978; No order number, William Ley, no address, 1981; No order number, Peter J. Penser, Lodi, NJ, 1982 [Following sheets go with this ‘Penser’]; Order 77-118, Mr. & Mrs. Fred W. Smith, Van Wert, OH, 1977; Order 74-034, no additional information; Order 77-007, no additional information,1977-1982, undated (Box 209, Folder 188)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Kensington; Order 79-002, Charles Brewers, Westland, MI 1978 [Separate sheet following, also 79-002, goes with this]; Order 79-035, Mr. & Mrs. J.F. Cobb, Ponca City, OK, 1979; Order 78-001, & 78-001A, Mr. & Mrs. Harry Daugherty, Huntley, IL, 1978; No order number, Mr. & Mrs. Carl Piotrowski, Tryon, OK, 1977; Order 80-004, Mark & Carol Patrzebowski, no additional information; No order number, Malcolm B. Smith, Sylvania, OH, 1979; No order number, Donald L. Stockdale, Weogufka, AL, 1977; Order 77-056, Harvey Walter, Cass City, MI, 1977,1977-1979, undated (Box 209, Folder 189)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Kenton; No order number, Mr. & Mrs. C.J. Orzechowski, Madison, OH,1978 (Box 210, Folder 190)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Kenwood; Order 79-020, Mr. & Mrs. Jerry O’Brien, Blissfield, MI, 1979; No order number, Thomas Schnipke, Ft. Jennings, OH, 1977,1977-1979 (Box 210, Folder 191)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Lamar; Order 77-008, Mr. & Mrs. William Raffette, Island Lake, IL,1976 (Box 210, Folder 192)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Laredo; Order 78-023, Mr. & Mrs. Carl Charlson, Chesterton, IN, 1978; Order 78-005, Mr. & Mrs. Arthur Dubbelstein, Clare, MI, 1978; No order number, Mrs. Norman Kuhn, Highland Park, IL, 1975,1975, 1978 (Box 210, Folder 193)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Lorain,undated (Box 210, Folder 194)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Manchester; No order number, Mrs. Ken Lyon, Dawn, MO,undated (Box 210, Folder 195)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Nassau; Order 77-050, Mr. & Mrs. Ronald Montania, Chesterton, IN, 1977; No order number, Mr. & Mrs. Mario Rotundo, Warren, MI, 1978,1977, 1978 (Box 210, Folder 196)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Newton; Order 79-008, Mr. & Mrs. Maurice Tomkins, Boyne City, MI,1979 (Box 210, Folder 197)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Normandy; No order number, Hyder Aly, McLean, VA, undated; No order number, Mr. & Mrs. Michael Davis, Roanoke, IN, 1977/78; No order number, Leonard Weinstein, Stanhope, NJ, 1978,1977-1978 (Box 211, Folder 198)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Oakland; No order number, Edward Amory, Greensprings, OH, 1976; Order 77-097, Douglas J. Bennet, Washington, D.C. 1977; No order number, Mr. & Mrs. Everett French, Ipava, IL, 1977; Order 69-031, no additional information,1976-1977, undated (Box 211, Folder 199)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Orlando; Order 77-117, C.E. McClenning, Camden, AK, 1977, Order 68-178, no additional information, Order 69-111, no additional information, Order 70-035, no additional information,1977, undated (Box 211, Folder 200)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Parkwood; Order 77-003, Mr. & Mrs. Harwood Brown, Three Rivers, MI,1977 (Box 211, Folder 201)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Plaza; No order number, Victor Bond, Ferndale, MI, undated; Order 78-029, Tom Domsic, Wyoming, MI, 1978; No order number, John Epsin, Winter Graden, FL, 1979; No order number, Melvin V. Franklin, Flint, MI, 1981; Garage for Plaza (2 plans),1978-1981, undated (Box 211, Folder 202)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Princeton; Order 77-059, John D. Heath, Marysville, OH, 1977; Order 78-032, James A. Hinkel, Dry Fork, WV, 1978; Order 79-014, Mr & Mrs. Fred Schmidt, Chebanse, IL, 1979; No order number, Lester Smith, Jr. Amburgey, KY, 1978; Order 72-053, no additional information; Order 71-153, garage; “Used on order 74-123,” 1974, No order number, garage, 1969,1969-1979, undated (Box 211, Folder 203)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Redwood; Order 64-078, Robert T. Desjardin, Williamstown, NJ.,1964 (Box 211, Folder 204)
  - Records, Plans for Special Orders - Regency; Order 77-031, Mr. & Mrs. Michael Ayers, Baltimore, OH, 1977; No order number, Mr. & Mrs. Mark Bezler, Preston, MD, 1977; No order number, Frank Gorski/Denise Rosenblum, Wanatah, IN, 1977; Order 79-027, Mr. & Mrs. David Kersh, Ottawa, OH, 1979; No order number, Mr. & Mrs. James Matthews, San Francisco, CA, 1977; No order number, Mr. & Mrs. Richard Peters, Union, IL, 1978; Order 79-003, Michael Schaffer, Elkhart, IN, 1979; Order 78-028, no additional information,1977-1979, undated (Box 211, Folder 205)